http://www.testek.com/privacy-policy?hsLang=en

PURPOSE
TESTEK SOLUTIONS is responsible for this website. TESTEK SOLUTIONS is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to this website. TESTEK SOLUTIONS has implemented technical, administrative, and physical measures to safeguard any personal information that we may collect.
This Privacy Policy describes TESTEK SOLUTIONS’ practices related to personal information collected through this website and applies to all visitors of this website.
SCOPE OF COLLECTED PERSONAL INFORMATION
TESTEK SOLUTIONS monitors user traffic patterns throughout the website according to a user’s domain name, browser type, date and time of access, and pages viewed. Our Web servers collect the domain names but not the email addresses of visitors. This information is collected in order to measure the number of visitors to our website and to determine which areas of the website users find useful based upon the amount of traffic to particular areas. TESTEK SOLUTIONS uses this information to enhance users’ experience at the website and to better prepare future content based on the interests of users.
A visitor to our website may be asked to provide personal information to receive a response or some other service from TESTEK SOLUTIONS. The personal information that you may be requested to provide includes your name, email address, physical address, the company you work for and any other information you choose to provide. The collection of information will be transparent to you – you will be asked for it and will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to provide it. If you choose not to provide any of the personal information requested, TESTEK SOLUTIONS may be unable to complete the transaction you have requested. To use certain sections of our website, you must register. If you register, we will require that you provide additional contact information. You will not be able to register without providing that information.
Your mobile provider may have a conflicting privacy position that captures personal information when you visit our website, but TESTEK SOLUTIONS is not responsible for and does not control how other parties may collect your information when you access our website.
USE OF COLLECTED PERSONAL INFORMATION
Personal information collected will only be used to:
conduct basic business operations, such as communicate with customers and business planning;
provide investor services;
provide the information, item, or service you have requested;
communicate with you about products, services, and events relating to TESTEK SOLUTIONS;
improve our products, services, and websites;
evaluate your interest in and/or allow you to apply for employment with TESTEK SOLUTIONS;
verify your identity to ensure security for one of the other purposes listed here;
ensure or enhance the security of TESTEK SOLUTIONS’ electronic systems;
protect against fraud;
screen against sanctions and antiterrorism lists as required by law;
respond to a legitimate legal request from law enforcement authorities or other government regulators;
investigate suspected or actual illegal activity;
prevent physical harm or financial loss;
support the sale or transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets (including through bankruptcy); and/or
conduct investigations to ensure compliance with, and comply with, legal obligations.
Except where used in support of a contract with you or to fulfill a legal obligation, our use of your personal information will be only for legitimate business interests as set forth above.
TESTEK SOLUTIONS may use the personal information you provide to contact you about products, services, promotions, special offers, surveys, and other information that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive such communications, please use the “unsubscribe” function within the website or let us know by sending an email to aerospace@testek.com. Also, TESTEK SOLUTIONS will ensure that any marketing communications sent by electronic means will provide a simple method for you to opt-out or unsubscribe. If you unsubscribe from marketing communications, you may continue to receive communications about your account or transactions with us.
STORAGE OF COLLECTED PERSONAL INFORMATION
Because TESTEK SOLUTIONS is a global company with locations and representatives in many different countries, we may transfer your information from one country to another within TESTEK SOLUTIONS, our affiliates and corporate representatives in order to accomplish the purposes listed above. These countries include, at a minimum, the United States, the many of the member states of the European Union, Canada, and other countries, including some in Asia. We will transfer your personal information consistent with applicable laws and regulations related to the protection of personal information worldwide.
TRANSFER OF COLLECTED PERSONAL INFORMATION
TESTEK SOLUTIONS may share your Personal Information with our affiliated companies. TESTEK SOLUTIONS will not sell or otherwise share your personal information outside of TESTEK SOLUTIONS, our affiliates and corporate representatives, except to:
service providers TESTEK SOLUTIONS  has retained to perform services on our behalf. TESTEK SOLUTIONS  will only share your personal information with service providers whom TESTEK SOLUTIONS  has contractually restricted from using or disclosing the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements;
comply with legal obligations, including but not limited to in response to a legitimate legal request from law enforcement authorities, courts, or other government regulators or authorities;
investigate suspected or actual illegal activity;
prevent physical harm or financial loss; or
support the sale or transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets (including through bankruptcy).
Your personal information may also be maintained and processed by our service providers in countries other than the one in which it was collected, such as the United States, member states of the European Union, Canada, and other jurisdictions.
RETENSION OF COLLECTED PERSONAL INFORMATION
TESTEK SOLUTIONS will retain personal information as long as needed to comply with its contractual and legal obligations. If the personal information is not subject to contractual or legal obligations, TESTEK SOLUTIONS will retain the data for as long as is required for the original purpose for which it was collected.
USE OF COOKIES OR OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES
TESTEK SOLUTIONS may use cookies on this website. Cookies are small text files sent to and stored on users’ computers that allow websites to recognize repeat users, facilitate users’ access to websites, and allow websites to compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements. Cookies do not damage users’ computers or files. If you do not want cookies to be accessible by this website, you should adjust the settings on your browser program to deny or disable the use of cookies.
This website may also use web beacons. A web beacon is usually a pixel on a website that can used to track whether a user has visited a particular website to deliver targeted advertising. Web beacons are used in combination with cookies, which means that, if you turn off your browser’s cookies, the web beacons will not be able to track your activity. The web beacon will still count a Website visit, but your unique information will not be recorded.
TESTEK SOLUTIONS may also use cookies and similar technology placed by one of our business partners to enable TESTEK SOLUTIONS to learn which advertisements bring users to our website.
THIRD PARTY LINKS
In some instances, TESTEK SOLUTIONS may provide links to non-TESTEK SOLUTIONS controlled websites, which TESTEK SOLUTIONS will make reasonable efforts to identify as such. TESTEK SOLUTIONS does not control such third-party websites, however, and cannot be responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other websites.
ADDITIONAL INFORMATION
Parents, Guardians, and Children: This website is intended for visitors who are at least 18 years of age and the age of majority in their jurisdiction of residence. TESTEK SOLUTIONS does not knowingly solicit information from, or market products or services to, children. If you do not meet the age requirements set out above, please do not enter your personal information on this or any other TESTEK SOLUTIONS website.
Users from California: Annually California residents may request and obtain information that TESTEK SOLUTIONS shared with other businesses for their own direct marketing use within the prior calendar year (as defined by California’s “Shine the Light Law”). If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which TESTEK SOLUTIONS shared this information in the immediately preceding calendar year. To obtain this information, please send an email message to aerospace@testek.com with “California Shine the Light Privacy Request” in the subject line as well as in the body of your message.
Users from the European Union: You have the right to lodge a complaint with your national or state data protection authority, which may also be known as a supervisory authority. You also have the right to request access to and correction or erasure of your personal information, seek restrictions on or object to the processing of certain personal information, and seek data portability under certain circumstances. To contact TESTEK SOLUTIONS about a request to access, correct, erase, object or seek restrictions or portability, please use the contact methods indicated at the end of this policy.
Users from the United States: TESTEK SOLUTIONS does not collect Social Security Numbers through its websites. TESTEK SOLUTIONS does, however, collect Social Security Numbers where required by law, such as for tax and payroll purposes for its employees. When TESTEK SOLUTIONS collects and/or uses Social Security Numbers, TESTEK SOLUTIONS will take proper care by protecting confidentiality, limiting access on a need-to-know basis, and implementing appropriate technical safeguards and retention plans.
PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES
As TESTEK SOLUTIONS expands and improves this website, we may need to update this policy. This policy may be modified from time to time without prior notice. We encourage you to review this policy on a regular basis for any changes. Substantive changes will be identified at the top of the policy.
CONTACT TESTEK SOLUTIONS
If you wish to access, correct, or update your personal information, if you have any comments or questions, or if there are other things we can do to maximize the value of this website to you, please email aerospace@testek.com. If you have questions about TESTEK SOLUTIONS’ privacy practices in general, please email aerospace@testek.com.
For more than 50 years, Testek Solutions has designed, manufactured, and supported highly reliable aerospace and defense test equipment and testing facilities for OEMs, MROs, and operators.
Test Solutions
OEMs
MROs
Integrators
About Testek
Technical Support
About Us
Contact Us
